♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
Come here, give me a kiss.
Hey! Stop that!
So, I'm semi-rejected by you now, huh?
[Chiquita] What's your group's name?
Oh, we are the…
[all] Karayom Kweens!
And your name is?
Chiquita?!
You stole my boyfriend.
I'm prettier than you!
[jeering]
No matter what, we need to beat them.
[Velma] I got you.
What do you need?
There are missing children,
and we suspect
they were taken to Velora Bay.
[Emerson] We need to win
this contest to get there.
I don't believe you.
No. What I'm saying is true.
[Chiquita] Step aside.
- [audience cheering]
- [Trinity] This is the fiercest,
and the most fabulous
drag showdown of the year,
the Reyna Royale Rumble!
[audience cheering]
[Tiny] The Glitter Bombz!
[thuds]
[audience cheering]
PREVIOUSLY
- [thudding]
- [audience whooping]
Come on!
Let's welcome to the stage…
The Karayom Kweens!
[audience cheering]
[music continues]
Looks like we'll have a tough time.
[in English] This is the moment
we've all been waiting for.
With a jaw-breaking score of 92.7…
Oh, my god! I'm so nervous!
- [audience cheering]
- [Trinity laughing]
[Atoy] Give this to us, Lord.
I just want my children back.
I just want a chance
to rebuild our family.
[music fades]
It's none other than…
[Velma] Karayom Kweens!
[rousing music playing]
And still the reigning queens
of Royale Rumble!
The Glitter Bombz!
Come on!
[exclaiming]
[Trinity] Congratulations,
The Glitter Bombz!
Wow! Still the champion!
[Trinity chuckles]
Congratulations, The Glitter Bombz!
[audience applauding]
[theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[thumps & gunshots]
- [music intensifies]
- [clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[music fades]
[muffled chatter in the distance]
[in English] And I beg to disagree!
They can't win,
because someone lost their life earlier…
- Right!
- …in their performance!
[jeering]
My goodness!
What now, Velma?
Shut up! Rawr!
It's in the rules of this competition
that no animals should be harmed!
Eh, what's this?
[audience] Ohh!
[audience] Whoa!
Look, everyone!
[awing & gasping]
I saw under the table earlier
the pitiful and lifeless dove
used in your performance.
- [music swells]
- [awing & gasping]
[music continues]
It's dead!
[jeering]
This is animal cruelty!
And they should be disqualified!
Right!?
- [jeering]
- [music swells]
That's right!
What's the use of having talent
if it won't wake up ever again?!
[squeals]
Shut up!
You jealous frogs!
You're just envious because we won!
- [audience] Ohh!
- You shut up, huh!
Because rules are not meant to be broken!
Hey! I'll break your ugly face!
[jeering]
[sneaky music playing]
Try it, girl!
Uh-huh! Hmm.
That's probably why
you're three-time champions,
because you're cheaters!
- [Nestor] Right! Cheaters!
- [Emerson] You're cheaters!
[Trinity] Okay! Wait, wait, wait!
Listen, listen!
Okay, okay.
We have a decision.
Because the rules were violated…
we declare that
Karayom Kweens is the winner!
- [audience cheering]
- [sneaky music playing]
Congratulations, Karayom Kweens!
- [audience cheering]
- [music continues]
Rules are rules! Okay?
So, no fighting.
Because at the end of the day,
you're all beautiful, you're all talented!
- [Emerson] Yes!
- They're all amazing!
Don't you think?
[audience] Yes!
Right? So once again, give it up for…
The Karayom Kweens!
- [audience cheering]
- [sneaky music playing]
Thank you.
Because of this, I can save my kids.
- [audience cheering]
- Let's stand by this, okay?
- Of course, of course.
- Okay.
- [Nestor] Game.
- [Emerson] Let's go.
[all] Karayom Kweens!
- [audience cheering]
- [music continues]
Can you believe it, we actually won!
Oh, you know,
I still can't believe we're the winners.
Yes. And thank goodness,
the Lord heard our prayer earlier.
- [Gavin] Right.
- Yes.
We're amazing,
we're amazing, we're amazing.
- [Paldo] I still can't believe it.
- Congratulations!
[Emerson] My prayer earlier was heard.
- [audience cheering]
- [Trinity] There!
Thank you! Thank you!
[audience cheering]
Once again, our new champion!
The Karayom Kweens take the stage!
[audience cheering]
[audience] Karayom Kweens! Karayom Kweens!
[exclaiming & laughing]
[music continues]
Oh! Brother Kurt, hold this!
[phone ringing]
- [all] Karayom Kweens!
- Hello?
- Hello-- Audrey?
- [all] Karayom Kweens!
- Huh?!
- [Emerson] Take our picture!
Take our picture!
You, you, you, take our picture here.
- Take our picture.
- [action music playing]
That's it, that's it,
that's it, take our picture.
That's it, that's it.
[lively chatter & cheering]
- [phone rings]
- [grunts]
[in English] Hello, Mr. Red Regalia!
Yes. Mr. Kalaf is sick today,
so he's resting.
Yes.
But he's expecting you to wire transfer
his payment tonight.
No delays allowed.
Okay. Will do that.
Mr. Kalaf
will expect your delivery on his birthday.
Okay? So, your goods
are in one of the villas, right?
You will see Mr. Kalaf at Velora Bay.
Bring your wife, Sir Red.
She will enjoy it there.
Okay. Give my regards to Boss K, okay?
I will. So, if there are
any requests, just call me.
Thank you.
Wait. I'm going to send you
a picture. Okay?
[suspicious music playing]
[Red on the phone] Watch him.
He might try to infiltrate Velora Bay.
That's a problem.
[Trinity on the phone] I don't know him.
But I'll forward this
to the head of security.
Don't worry, sir.
No undesirables have
entered Boss K's island.
If he shows up,
he will be killed on the spot,
and his body fed
to Boss K's crocodile pets.
- Thank you.
- All right, Mr. Regalia.
[music swells]
Oh, well! Not that I'm bragging, okay?
But if not for me,
we wouldn't be able to beat Glitter Bombz!
- [woman] Oh! Right!
- Thanks, Ma! Thanks!
- [lively chatter]
- [Velma] You're welcome!
And because of that, I'm buying drinks!
- Whoa!
- [lively chatter]
Pineapple!
- [exclaims]
- Yes!
- [woman] That's right! That's right!
- I thought… you're alcohol-free now.
[Nestor] No!
- Just kidding, just kidding.
- Oh, that's enough!
Better for us to chat in Tabang Lupa.
- Okay!
- Okay, oh.
Wait.
Where are Brother Atoy and Papa Uno?
[sneaky music playing]
[Nestor] Where are they?
Two access points.
Via helicopter, via boat.
But because of that radar tower,
we can't enter without being detected.
That means we can't deploy
first strikers here,
because even a pump boat will be spotted.
The only way is to disable their radar
and communication systems.
Sir…
I can infiltrate that.
I just need step-by-step instructions
to hack their computers.
That will be the easy part of the job,
because our IT team already
prepared for it.
All you have to do…
is plug this into their computer.
[music continues]
Once you do that,
our IT team can access their system.
Nice. Plug and play.
[Mercado] Now…
my biggest concern is that
the people with you are not trained.
[action music playing]
This is very risky.
They must follow protocol,
even if they're civilians.
Padua, their lives are in your hands.
[music continues]
I'll take care of them, sir.
I'll make sure they're ready.
[music swells]
[waves crashing]
[lively chatter]
[music continues]
[Emerson] I like it here.
[lively chatter]
Welcome to Velora Bay, queens!
Ah, correction!
- It's…
- [all] Karayom Kweens!
[giggling]
[pleasant music playing]
[chuckles]
[Atoy] Hey!
Your security here is so intense,
we feel really safe, but that's okay.
At least, the girls and I are safe.
Yes, correct!
[receptionist] Michael V, is that you?
Ah-- ah, well--
Joy! Just call me Joy.
I'm not Michael V.
There's no taping today
for Bubble Gang or Pepito.
- [Nestor] You're not sure.
- Oh, joke.
- [laughs]
- [Atoy] Thank you, mmm.
Oh, by the way… Uh, where--
where's our room, for the girls?
[receptionist] Yes. Villa number seven
has been reserved for you.
We advise you to be quiet
and no loud music, please.
- [others] Oh, oh.
- [receptionist] Because you are very near
the villa of Princess Putri
of the Amrati Kingdom.
- [gasps]
- [Gavin] Oh, my god.
Oh! There's a princess here!
- [Emerson] Really?!
- [giggles]
[Paldo] Can we meet her?
[giggles]
[receptionist] Unfortunately, no.
- [Paldo gasps]
- She's sick,
and she can't even make it to the party.
[others] Aww…
[Paldo] Sad, sad.
[receptionist] Also,
before we assist you to your villa,
we need you to sign first our NDA.
Oh! NBA! So many boys there!
- [laughing]
- [lively chatter]
NDA.
Ahh, NDA!
[laughs]
What's that?
It's non-disclosure agreement, sis.
- Smart.
- [Kurt] Why?
What kind of party
is this going to be, ah?
Because I'm getting
a little excited already.
[laughs]
[receptionist] It's just a normal,
normal party.
But it'll be like Vegas.
Ohh!
It's like, it's like, it's like,
what happens in Velora, stays in Velora!
- [lively chatter]
- [laughing]
[receptionist]
All right, queens, are you ready?
- [others] Ready! Let's go!
- [receptionist] Let's go!
[lively chatter]
[Paldo] Go, girls!
[music continues]
[Emerson] Ye-hey!
[music fades]
The CCTV are all outside.
Inside, there's none.
Okay. Come on, hurry up.
Do your makeup and get dressed.
Remember… We are the main event;
we are also the main distraction.
So, we need to do our best.
- [Atoy] Let's go.
- Sureness, Ato--
[clears throat] I mean, uhm, exactly.
- Exactly, 'Toy.
- [Atoy] Okay.
After you get dressed, mingle first.
We need to keep a low profile, huh.
Copy?
Atoy, how can we keep a low profile?
Look at us.
We might end up being courted there later.
Oh, oh-- and the theme is Bollywood.
We'll shake it out there, joke.
Uno, you need to disable the comm system.
So the first striker team can be alerted.
Once they know,
they can penetrate the island.
They can move around,
maybe find where the children are.
- -[Atoy] All right?
- Yes, sir.
Okay. Let's move, let's move!
I'll just bring out the guns.
[pensive music playing]
- [clatters]
- [Karla] Ouch!
- Who's that?!
- [gasps]
- Get out!
- [rousing music playing]
- Karla!
- That hurt.
Son of a thread!
Karla, what are you doing here?!
Karla, it's dangerous here!
Eh, why are you allowed to come?!
Sorry, Brother Atoy. I just
really want to help rescue my niece.
You, you're so stubborn, huh?
Stay here!
Don't leave this room, you're not coming!
Come on, come on!
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Aren't you supposed to be
with the Karayom Kweens?
Why are you dressed like a bodyguard?
Who are you guarding?
Bodyguard?
[soft rock music playing]
You. I'll guard you.
Me?! Eh, why me?
[music continues]
[children wailing]
- [goon 1] Hurry, get inside!
- [goon 2] Inside, inside!
[goon 1] Hurry!
[goon 1] Stay there, stay there!
You're so stubborn, huh!
- Be quiet!
- Stop it!
If you don't stop, I'll shoot all of you!
[children wailing]
You?! You won't stop?!
You're so noisy, huh!
[children wailing]
[goon 2] You, be quiet!
[goon 1] Stop it!
- Trust me…
- [goon 1] You're so irritating!
- …we'll escape from here.
- [goon 1] Mmph, you're stubborn, huh!
Huh? Escape?
What will you do?
Just stay quiet.
- [goon 1] Quiet!
- [goon 2] You're all so hard-headed!
Ibyang, what will we do?
- Just stay quiet.
- [goon 2] You're crying again.
Uh…
Brother, brother,
can I go to the bathroom?
I really need to pee.
Go pee in the corner.
Ah--
Uhm…
Eh, it's not pee,
It's number two, actually!
You're just fooling us.
Oh. No, promise, ah-
Gosh! It's coming out, it's coming out!
- [goon 2] She might make a mess here.
- Come on, come on, come on!
I'll go with you!
[suspicious music playing]
Hurry!
[music continues]
[goon 1] Stop it already! You're so noisy!
[music fades]
[hip-hop upbeat music playing]
Hmm, look at these people.
Wait, wait, wait.
[music fades]
Look at that.
[mysterious music playing]
The court has released a warrant of arrest
for Former Mayor Rizaldo Coloma,
the alleged bagman of corrupt senators.
That's Rizaldo Coloma, right?
He's the corrupt mayor
and the… the bagman!
[music continues]
That's why we have an NDA.
- [gasps]
- So we won't say who's here.
[music continues]
Can you believe that?
[Emerson chuckles]
So that's why.
That bastard is hiding here.
- Hey.
- Would be nice to smash--
- [sneaky music playing]
- You're even eating here.
[mumbles] I'm hiding it already, eh.
Stop that.
[somber music playing]
[tense music playing]
Atoy, my dear…
where's Uno?
He split from us earlier.
We talked through the earpiece.
[music swells]
Eh, where's Karla?
[sneaky music playing]
Raise it a little higher,
raise it a little higher.
[Atoy clears throat]
Hello, Ma'am.
[music continues]
My dear, you look so interesting.
I'm Mrs. Villaforte.
And you are?
Uh, um… apologies for not introducing her.
She is Princess Putri of Amrati.
She is a princess?
No wonder she looks magnificent.
Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[Atoy clears throat]
Did I hear princess?
Yes. Meet the princess of Amrati.
- Oh.
- Excuse me.
It's very nice to meet you.
You know, my husband
would've loved to meet you too.
[heavy music playing]
Too bad, we're here on business.
Ah, what kind of business?
You do monkey business?
[music intensifies]
Excuse me.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
My necklace?
[music continues]
[music fades]
[soft rock music playing]
Rizaldo Coloma, the mayor in hiding?
[Mercado] Yes.
The corrupt mayor, bagman of the senators.
So, you're here too, you animal?
[music continues]
You even joined forces, you two demons.
Mr. Ambassador.
Oh, Senator.
- How--
- Do you remember my wife?
Yes, ah--
[suspicious music playing]
- Hey!
- [thuds]
Aren't you done yet?!
Eh, I'll take even longer.
You're disturbing me, eh.
I can't concentrate.
[music continues]
[goon 1] Let's finish this.
Put medicine in that batch.
[goon 2] What's this for? Vitamins?
[goon 1] Sleeping pills.
So the children will sleep.
So they'll be easier
to load onto the ship.
They won't wake up until tomorrow.
[music fades]
[device blips]
[ominous music playing]
- [swishes]
- [groans]
Ouch.
- [music continues]
[goon 2] Oh, your food!
At least the children
have something to eat!
[goon 2] Do you want some?
Take some.
[goon 1] No.
[goon 2] Hey, eat up!
[goon 1] Be quiet!
Here's your food!
You don't even want to eat!
[heavy music playing]
Eat now!
- [music continues]
- [children sobbing]
[tense music playing]
Surprised to see me?
[ominous music playing]
[Red] It's a small world.
Turns out you wronged both me and Samir.
Where are the children?
[tense music playing]
- [electronic blipping]
- [intense music playing]
You want to get back at me, don't you?
Revenge!
[thumping]
[grunting & groaning]
[theme music playing]
This is Tonet and her brother.
How did they end up here?
Madame, maybe you're being haunted.
That's the one
you killed at the mall, right?
- [music continues]
- [groans]
UP NEXT
- Tatoy!
- [Atoy] My child?
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
Ibyang!
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias